# Omar Jakmira

## Full Stack Developer



Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with a wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend and mobile development requirements. Able to handle any part of the process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 6 years of related experience.

## Work History

#### 2016-12 -Current

## Full Stack Freelancer Developer

Khamsat.com

- Developed user-oriented visuals and features using front-end languages, including HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Used programming capabilities in PHP, C#, SQL and JavaScript and other libraries as needed.

#### 2020-10 -2021-1

## Senior Software Developer

Toriom.com

- Developed Laravel and Vuejs applications
- integrate existing apps with 3rd party API (Aman API, SendGrid, STC API)

#### 2020-8 -2020-9

## Senior Javascript Developer

Larsa.org

 working on js micro services that will integrate with an existing system (Survey, Payment service)

#### 2019-03 -2020-03

## Senior Mobile Developer

OPStudioz, damascus

 Created custom mobile applications using cross-platform technologies.

#### 2015-12 -2019-03

## IT Technician

Al Rasheed, damascus

- Managed system-wide operating system and software deployments, as well as related software upgrade problems.
- Established, repaired and optimized networks by installing wiring, cabling and devices.
- Explained technical information in clear terms to non-technical individuals to promote better understanding..
- Patched software and installed new versions to eliminate security problems and protect data.

### Education

## 2017-01 - Faculty of Media

Current

Open Learning- Damascus

## Featured Seller on Khamsat.com

Featured seller on khamsat.com with 100% service evaluation

## Online Portfolio

power19942.github.io

## Links

github.com/power19942

khamsat.com/user/omar-jaqmira

#### Contact

#### Address

Damascus

#### Phone

+963962462090

#### E-mail

omar.jakmira@gmail.com

#### Birthdate

1994

#### Skills

#### Back-End

PHP Laravel

.NET CORE

Node.js

## Front-End

JS, HTML, CSS

React + Next.js

Vuejs

0000

Angular 8

PWA

#### Mobile

Flutter

React Native

Android + Kotlin

Database

SQL DB

MongoDB

## DevOps

Docker

CI / CD

Kubernetes

## Others

Firebase

Git

Elastic stack

TDD

Unit Testing

Nginx

Linux

Microservices